{
    "id": "deade87d219c431b9807ce4bba0000a8",
    "title": "Will, Would, Can, Could",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "3fa4196cc12449fabf9f131f886a9f62",
            "title": "Can, Could, Will, Would",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He ran as fast as he ………………………..",
                    "description": "Could indicates past ability.",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "wouldCol"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She …………………………… swim when she was just three.",
                    "description": "Could indicates past ability.",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Raju ……………………….. speak six languages.",
                    "description": "Can is used to make a request, to ask for permission or to express ability to do something.",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t think I ………………………….. pass the test.",
                    "description": "Will is used to predict something, to express willingness or to announce a spontaneous decision.",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "could",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He failed the test because he …………………………….. answer only 2 questions.",
                    "description": "Could shows past ability.",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He said that he ……………………….. help but he didn’t.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I had enough money, I ………………………….. travel around the world.",
                    "description": "Would is the past form of will.",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "can"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I were you, I …………………………… get that mole examined.",
                    "description": "Would is the past form of will.",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "can",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ………………………….. borrow my car if you want.",
                    "description": "Can is used to make a request, to ask for permission or to express ability to do something.",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "will",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who ……………………………. cook dinner today?",
                    "description": "Will is used to predict something, to express willingness or to announce a spontaneous decision.",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………… you like to dance with me?",
                    "description": "Would is used in polite requests.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Will",
                        "Would",
                        "Could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I tried to solve the problem, but I …………………………...",
                    "description": "Could not shows past inability. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "cannot",
                        "could not",
                        "would not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}